Special major, obviously the council. The term thing works for this year is 24-24 years ago
The main problem was being discussed by those city councils in particular they've worked at four or eight points of work and
I'm sorry about that too but uh...I believe it's needed to raise together growth gather so
i have my bachelor's first Christmas grant pleasure two communication.
question right man.
Father God will love you, I've got to be known that all the earth is yours and everything within it
So we come through tonight with your own university
We do ask for your blessing in Your provision
And god would as that's a good way of doing why stewards about You plus this
With
But maybe make me be a community like those grown together
They can seem just to see
Your prosperity here. So we just ask a wisdom piece, unity and your
Reaction if you ever too far eyes on You
We will grow in the new plus
Help us to be like Jesus
This is my bread
I'm glad that you're willing to do what
The United States is my friend
To the Republic for which it stands
Well, I nation and i have an individual
Whether it's a dangerous thing or
We have two types of personal reading this day and with
Please do announce that we extended an offer
Of a compromise arena which has been accepted by the boys in girls club
Where you look forward to a friendly and productive relationship
To be club
In future
Thank You
Second payment in The Garce
The evening council
We'll have the boys in Russell of Ottawa County
Where police to present a plan to cancel tonight
It represents compromise between all the innocent parties
we'd like
To thank your representative of friends and co-man
We spent time with us yesterday afternoon
And an attempt for each resolution
We'll also point out that you're
Another version of the lease
Underneath your package
That's one
And we will not be using based on
The announcements
Although it has attachment A
But is a legal description
The land thats being released
Attached to get
The attention of the agreement
We'll see what we can do
That's a good thing
So
Interpacking the amendment to
What that up there is
First of all, the lease agreement which
They redline copy which shows
All our lives to this
Means behind that
The attention of the lease agreement
And the reason you have
Intention for these things
Because there are some
Things that will be settled in your future
Quickly and a future
Those who build into the lease agreement
But if any opposed contingencies
You can't come to pass
Of the Morgan John, you need a market control
If those contingencies do not come
To pass
We cannot accomplish
The lease agreement that we're all
And disdain and they are all looking for
Then this contingent base of agreement will
Come into the land
For attachments
That is the agreement
Which is a different agreement
That has the one that's attached to
Back on it
It takes all things
They don't have their
Attached on they
Then attachments
Through E
You can have real life of
So I wanted
To filter through your old
Added in the amount of order
To the land
So that I think might there are any questions
If you want to have your question
Through me
Yes
Motion
For rough head
We approve both of these agreement and contingent
Intention, lease agreement with
The boys in girls club, the club, the county
And authorize an heir
To execute same subject
To lease agreement, the child
The priority of agreement and the child
Lingling funding
Be only legally funded agreements
Between parties
Unless in until any one on more contingencies
Listed in paragraph five A
That lease agreement is determined by
The city
In which day to have failed
I set out in that agreement
And back case
Between the parties
And then party will
Then act according to
The party's called
Settard of Williamson
Don't go on
Part four
Motion to adjourn
Settard